

JR Web Developer: After a period of 10 years working on a commercial part of banks and advertising agencies, today I'm realizing a dream of becoming a Web Developer. I'm currently developing on the front-end, applying knowledge that I've acquired through courses and on my own.

RODRIGO ROSA

Phone:

+55(48)99136-2161

E-Mail: rodrigorosa.dev@gmail.com
Github: https://github.com/rodrigocros
Linkedin:https://www.linkedin.com/in/rodri

go-rosa-21780a45/

Education

- Bachelor Business Administration
 CIESA Manaus | 2007-2011
- MBA Project management.
 UEA Manaus | 2014- 2016.
- JAVASCRIPT Udemy – 2021
- HTML + CSS. Udemy -2021
- AngularUdemy 2022
- Angular + C#
 DevinHouse 2022

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- manageable

Languages

Spanish English Portuguese

Experience

10/2021

Front-end Web Developer - Golabs, Florianópolis.

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Using languages skills, HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript and Angular.
- Using Bootstrap as a Framework.
- Visual Studio Code.
- Figma e PSD.

05/2017 – 11/2018

Account Management – Reweb, Manaus.

- Sale of Landing pages, Facebook ads, Google Ads, social media.
- Implementation of the products.
- Management of product quality.
- Control of customers' Google and Facebook credits.
- CRM usage training.
- Training for handling Inbound Leads (sales funnel). Cold call training.
- SPIN Selling usage training.

08/2013 - 04/2016

Commercial Management - Santander Bank, Manaus.

- Sale of financing and insurance and other bank products.
- Direct contact with store managers, sellers and customers.
- Negotiation of financing amounts.
- Payment of financed amount to the concessionaire.
- Collection of overdue installments.